[Music]
Those who crossed all limits for the country
Why should there be any border in the country for them
[Music]
[Praise]
We are also with them in need of our security day and night
[Music]
For whom we all are their own
After all, they too have some dreams for their own
Whose bravery we all owe It is
our duty too to encourage their progress
[Music] They
are bound by
some comfort in their daily life Perhaps they too
like it Because of
whose presence this sky and earth are safe And
soon our efforts will also be made to secure
their today and tomorrow
ICICI Defence Salary Account
with super benefits Special for our superhit